Everywhere I go
I feel so alive
Yeah
I'm happy
head to toe
I'm in overdrive
You're right
Clear those clouds away
I can feel the sun
Yeah
Let the music play
Now, we've just begun
I'm ready
'Cause these are the best days
(uh, yes, these are the best days)
These are the best days
(these are the best days)
(uh, that's right)
Of our lives
(C'mon)
(the best days of our lives)
There's magic in the air
And it feels so right
Yeah
So follow every day
And you'll see the light
Shine so bright
'Cause these are the best days
(uh, yes, these are the best days)
These are the best days
(these are the best days)
(uh, that's right)
Of our lives
(C'mon)
(Best days of our lives)
Yeah
Oh, can you feel the spotlight?
(feel the spotlight)
Shining on down, yeah, it's alright
(yeah, it's alright)
Living the moment and find
Your place in this world
Every boy, every girl, yeah
Follow your dreams, let them lead
Let them guide all you do
Let them see you through
And they'll see you through
'Cause these are the best days
(uh, yes, these are the best days)
These are the best days
(these are the best days)
(uh, that's right)
Of our lives
(C'mon)
(Best days of our lives)
Yeah
These are the best days
Oh, these are the best days
(These are the best days)
These are the best days
Oh, these are the best days
(These are the best days)
These are the best days
Oh, these are the best days
Of our lives
(Best days of our lives)
Of our lives, yeah
NOTE Of our lives, of our lives, yeah (best days of our lives, best days of our lives)